需要注意的是  我们要让我们的sunshine应用好100倍
On that note, we're going to make our sunshine app
通过连接网络上的OpenWeatherMap服务
100 times better now by connecting it over the network
OpenWeatherMap服务提供免费的气象数据和预报的API
to the OpenWeatherMap service. OpenWeatherMap provides a free weather data
并且链接就在下方  你可以点击查看
and forecast API. And the site is linked below, so
通过浏览这个站点
you can follow along. By scrolling through the site,
你可以看到什么类型的数据是可用的
you can see what type of data is available. It
它还有示例查询  你可以点击这里
also has example queries so you can click on this
去查看在英国伦敦的天气情况
one to see what the weather is like in London.
它包括一个天气状况的友好的用户说明
It includes a user friendly description of the weather
在这种情况下  比如多云
condition, such as broken clouds, in this case. And
我们在我们的应用中以后会使用到它
we'll use this later in our app. For the
对于完整的天气状况的列表  你可以返回到首页
full list of weather conditions, you can go back to
并且向下滚动  然后点击这个链接
the main page. And scroll down. And then, click
获取气象条件的代码
on this link here for the Weather Condition Codes.
在这个页面上  我们有了气象条件的完整列表
And on this page, we have the full list
它包含了所有的内容  从散云到过冷雨
of weather conditions. It contains everything, from scattered clouds to
甚至是火山灰  我不知道你那里的情况
freezing rain, or even volcanic ash. I don't know
但愿希望它不会经常发生
about you, but hopefully that doesn't happen too often.